class QuestionModel{
  final String question;
  final List<String> options;
  final correctAnswerIndex;
  final String Solution;

  const QuestionModel({
    required this.question,
    required this.options,
    required this.correctAnswerIndex,
    required this.Solution,
  });
}
List<QuestionModel> idiomatic_expression = [

  QuestionModel(question: "1. I'm afraid I can't make it to the party. I have too much on my plate.",
      options: [
        "A. I have too much on my table.",
        "B. I have too much on my agenda.",
        "C. I have too much on my bookshelf.",
        "D. I have too much on my lamp."
      ],
      correctAnswerIndex: 1,
      Solution: "The correct answer is B. 'I have too much on my plate' is an idiomatic expression that means being busy or having a lot of tasks to do."
  ),
  QuestionModel(question: "2. The new employee hit the ground running, impressing everyone with their dedication and hard work.",
      options: [
        "A. The new employee hit the ceiling crawling.",
        "B. The new employee hit the wall strolling.",
        "C. The new employee hit the floor sprinting.",
        "D. The new employee hit the road jogging."
      ],
      correctAnswerIndex: 2,
      Solution: "The correct answer is C. 'Hit the ground running' is an idiomatic expression that means starting a new activity or job energetically and successfully."
  ),
  QuestionModel(question: "3. The teacher advised the students to hit the books before the exam.",
      options: [
        "A. Hit the tables",
        "B. Hit the chairs",
        "C. Hit the shelves",
        "D. Hit the books"
      ],
      correctAnswerIndex: 3,
      Solution: "The correct answer is D. 'Hit the books' is an idiomatic expression that means to study or to start studying intensively."
  ),
  QuestionModel(question: "4. The manager pulled some strings to get the project approved ahead of schedule.",
      options: [
        "A. The manager pulled some cables.",
        "B. The manager pulled some wires.",
        "C. The manager pulled some chains.",
        "D. The manager pulled some strings."
      ],
      correctAnswerIndex: 3,
      Solution: "The correct answer is D. 'Pulling strings' is an idiomatic expression that means using influence or connections to achieve a goal."
  ),
  QuestionModel(question: "5. The sudden change in plans threw a wrench into our weekend getaway.",
      options: [
        "A. Threw a screwdriver",
        "B. Threw a hammer",
        "C. Threw a spanner",
        "D. Threw a wrench"
      ],
      correctAnswerIndex: 3,
      Solution: "The correct answer is D. 'Throw a wrench into the works' is an idiomatic expression that means to cause a problem or disrupt a plan."
  ),
  QuestionModel(question: "6. Let's keep this project under wraps until we have all the details sorted out.",
      options: [
        "A. Under the table",
        "B. Under the carpet",
        "C. Under the rug",
        "D. Under wraps"
      ],
      correctAnswerIndex: 3,
      Solution: "The correct answer is D. 'Under wraps' is an idiomatic expression that means keeping something secret or confidential."
  ),
  QuestionModel(question: "7. The athlete had to bite the bullet and undergo surgery to repair the injured knee.",
      options: [
        "A. Bite the knife",
        "B. Bite the sword",
        "C. Bite the gun",
        "D. Bite the bullet"
      ],
      correctAnswerIndex: 3,
      Solution: "The correct answer is D. 'Bite the bullet' is an idiomatic expression that means facing a difficult or unpleasant situation with courage."
  ),
  QuestionModel(question: "8. The comedian's jokes always hit the nail on the head, making the audience burst into laughter.",
      options: [
        "A. Hit the nail on the foot",
        "B. Hit the nail on the hand",
        "C. Hit the nail on the elbow",
        "D. Hit the nail on the head"
      ],
      correctAnswerIndex: 3,
      Solution: "The correct answer is D. 'Hit the nail on the head' is an idiomatic expression that means describing a situation accurately or getting to the main point."
  ),
  QuestionModel(question: "9. The team decided to go back to the drawing board after the initial plan failed.",
      options: [
        "A. Go back to the sketchpad",
        "B. Go back to the notebook",
        "C. Go back to the easel",
        "D. Go back to the drawing board"
      ],
      correctAnswerIndex: 3,
      Solution: "The correct answer is D. 'Go back to the drawing board' is an idiomatic expression that means starting a task over because the previous attempt failed."
  ),
  QuestionModel(question: "10. The politician tried to sweep the scandal under the rug, but it eventually came to light.",
      options: [
        "A. Sweep the dirt under the rug",
        "B. Sweep the mess under the rug",
        "C. Sweep the dust under the rug",
        "D. Sweep the scandal under the rug"
      ],
      correctAnswerIndex: 3,
      Solution: "The correct answer is D. 'Sweep under the rug' is an idiomatic expression that means attempting to hide or ignore something negative or embarrassing."
  ),
  QuestionModel(question: "11. The company decided to cut corners to reduce expenses, but it led to a decline in product quality.",
      options: [
        "A. Cut edges",
        "B. Cut curves",
        "C. Cut angles",
        "D. Cut corners"
      ],
      correctAnswerIndex: 3,
      Solution: "The correct answer is D. 'Cut corners' is an idiomatic expression that means to take shortcuts, often resulting in a lower quality outcome."
  ),
  QuestionModel(question: "12. After years of hard work, the artist's career finally took off.",
      options: [
        "A. Took the sky",
        "B. Took the clouds",
        "C. Took the stars",
        "D. Took off"
      ],
      correctAnswerIndex: 3,
      Solution: "The correct answer is D. 'Take off' is an idiomatic expression that means to become successful or start to be noticed and appreciated."
  ),
  QuestionModel(question: "13. The manager asked the team to think outside the box to come up with innovative solutions.",
      options: [
        "A. Think outside the rectangle",
        "B. Think outside the square",
        "C. Think outside the circle",
        "D. Think outside the box"
      ],
      correctAnswerIndex: 3,
      Solution: "The correct answer is D. 'Think outside the box' is an idiomatic expression that means thinking creatively or unconventionally."
  ),
  QuestionModel(question: "14. Despite the setbacks, the team decided to stick to their guns and pursue the original plan.",
      options: [
        "A. Stick to their swords",
        "B. Stick to their knives",
        "C. Stick to their shields",
        "D. Stick to their guns"
      ],
      correctAnswerIndex: 3,
      Solution: "The correct answer is D. 'Stick to your guns' is an idiomatic expression that means to remain firm and resolute in your beliefs or decisions."
  ),
  QuestionModel(question: "15. The sudden increase in demand caught the company off guard, and they struggled to meet orders.",
      options: [
        "A. Caught the company off balance",
        "B. Caught the company off center",
        "C. Caught the company off axis",
        "D. Caught the company off guard"
      ],
      correctAnswerIndex: 3,
      Solution: "The correct answer is D. 'Caught off guard' is an idiomatic expression that means being surprised or unprepared for something unexpected."
  ),
  QuestionModel(question: "16. The actor decided to play it by ear and see how the audition went before committing to the role.",
      options: [
        "A. Play it by nose",
        "B. Play it by mouth",
        "C. Play it by eye",
        "D. Play it by ear"
      ],
      correctAnswerIndex: 3,
      Solution: "The correct answer is D. 'Play it by ear' is an idiomatic expression that means making decisions as events unfold rather than planning in advance."
  ),
  QuestionModel(question: "17. The professor's explanation went over the students' heads, and they struggled to understand the complex theory.",
      options: [
        "A. Went over the students' hats",
        "B. Went over the students' caps",
        "C. Went over the students' helmets",
        "D. Went over the students' heads"
      ],
      correctAnswerIndex: 3,
      Solution: "The correct answer is D. 'Go over someone's head' is an idiomatic expression that means being too complex or difficult for someone to understand."
  ),
  QuestionModel(question: "18. The athlete wanted to get back on the horse after recovering from the injury.",
      options: [
        "A. Get back on the donkey",
        "B. Get back on the zebra",
        "C. Get back on the giraffe",
        "D. Get back on the horse"
      ],
      correctAnswerIndex: 3,
      Solution: "The correct answer is D. 'Get back on the horse' is an idiomatic expression that means to return to an activity after a failure or setback."
  ),
  QuestionModel(question: "19. The project is on thin ice, and any further delays could lead to its cancellation.",
      options: [
        "A. On thick ice",
        "B. On solid ice",
        "C. On stable ice",
        "D. On thin ice"
      ],
      correctAnswerIndex: 3,
      Solution: "The correct answer is D. 'On thin ice' is an idiomatic expression that means being in a risky or precarious situation."
  ),
  QuestionModel(question: "20. The team decided to nip the issue in the bud before it escalated into a major problem.",
      options: [
        "A. Nip the issue in the flower",
        "B. Nip the issue in the leaf",
        "C. Nip the issue in the stem",
        "D. Nip the issue in the bud"
      ],
      correctAnswerIndex: 3,
      Solution: "The correct answer is D. 'Nip it in the bud' is an idiomatic expression that means to address a problem or conflict at an early stage before it becomes more serious."
  ),


  ];